

PAULA LARA CYBERSECURITY ANALIST / GRAPHIC AND WEB DESIGNER

ABOUT ME

MI NOMBRE ES PAULA LARA

My journey as an autodidact began early in my life, shaped by homeschooling from the age of 6. Starting my formal education as a developer and networking specialist, my fascination with arts and design led me to specialize in UI/UX design. Continually driven by curiosity, I've expanded my skills in graphic and product design, methodologies, app and web development, photography, animation, and illustration, blending both digital and traditional techniques.

Renowned for my active and inquisitive mind, I possess a strong aptitude for learning. My passion for design is deeply rooted in aesthetics, geometric precision, and a keen eye for color theory. With a relentless attention to detail, I draw inspiration from the nuances of everyday life. I approach my work with fervor, finding joy in both collaborating with my team and embracing constructive feedback as a means of growth.

EDUCATION

Contemporary Design (Taught in English)

MBDesign MÁSTER (UPC)

This master's degree is focused on the study of the latest trends in design (graphic, architectural and product) and the work in multidisciplinary work groups for the resolution of space problems with special attention to social impact.

2020 - 2021 (45/60 credits completed)

Industrial Design Engineering

MBDesign MÁSTER (UPC)

Master focused on the production of final products through CAD modeling (Rhinoceros, CATIA, SketchUp, AutoCAD), 3D printing and programming with Arduino.

Design Thinking workshops developing products and solutions for real cases in collaboration with the company Danone. **2019-2020** (45/60 credits completed)

BSC (Honours) Computing & IT, pathway in Design

Bachelor (OPEN UNIVERSITY)

Computer and information technology. 4-year degree. Network and database administration, development of software solutions (AWS, Oracle). Application design with HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript. Principles of PHP.

2009-2013

Graphic Arts

Professional course (Escola Joso)

Drawing, storyboarding/scripting, color theory and application, comics, character creation and graphic design.

2012-2014

EXPERIENCE

IT Auditor

IT audits, including testing the design, implementation and effectiveness of general IT controls (GITC), automatic controls (ITAC) and information produced by the entity (IPE). Experience in SAP, NAVISION, and other ERP.

Process-based risk assessment, including fraud and error risk detection.

Sept. 2022 - Feb. 2024

Freelance

Web design and maintenance, graphic design, branding and illustration for different clients, among them: InfltrApp, Epysteme y Cloud App. *Jan.* 2019 - Aug. 2023

Cloud Security Analyst Coca-

Cola European Partners
Security threat analysis,
regulatory interpretation of
security incident response
centers and B2B
communication.

Septiembre 2021 - Dic. 2022

SKILLS

DESIGN TOOLS
WEB
DEVELOPMENT
ILLUSTRATION
VIDEO

Photoshop, Illustration, InDesign, Adobe XD CSS3, HTML 5, JavaScript Vector expert, Hand-drawing and coloring, Sketching

vector expert, Hand-drawing and coloring, Sketching

After Effects, Adobe Premiere

LANGUAGES

ESPAÑOL Materna CATALÁN 2da lengua INGLÉS Fluido

CERTIFICATES



MICROSOFT CERTIFIED: AZURE FUNDAMENTALS

Microsoft Expedition: dic. 2021



E-COMMERCE

Google Expedition: sept. 2019 ID: PP6 D6G RD5

LET'S CONNECT!

www.dribbble.com/paularalc

https://www.linkedin.com/in/paularac/